<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo website on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo website on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Erdan101.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create Github Repository</title>
      <link>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/cont/repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/cont/repo/</guid>
      <description>Create a repository on Github to store your Hugo website files.
Sign in to Github   Sign up for a GitHub account.
If you already have a Github account, just skip this step.
  Sign in to Github with your uername and password.
  Create a Repository   Click on New repository on the right of the page.
  Input Erdan101.github.io under Repository name.
  You must use a &amp;lt;USERNAME&amp;gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloy the Website</title>
      <link>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/cont/push/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/cont/push/</guid>
      <description>Rebuild the Site Run hugo to rebuild your site.
F:\Hugo\Sites\mysite&amp;gt; hugo Start building sites … | EN | ZH -------------------+----+----- Pages | 84 | 10 Paginator pages | 0 | 0 Non-page files | 21 | 0 Static files | 84 | 84 Processed images | 0 | 0 Aliases | 1 | 0 Sitemaps | 2 | 1 Cleaned | 0 | 0 Total in 590 ms The public/ directory will be generated right away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/credits/</guid>
      <description>Contributors Thanks to them for making Open Source Software a better place !
And a special thanks to @vjeantet for his work on docdock, a fork of hugo-theme-learn. v2.0.0 of this theme is inspired by his work.
Packages and libraries  mermaid - generation of diagram and flowchart from text in a similar manner as markdown font awesome - the iconic font and CSS framework jQuery - The Write Less, Do More, JavaScript Library lunr - Lunr enables you to provide a great search experience without the need for external, server-side, search services&amp;hellip; horsey - Progressive and customizable autocomplete component clipboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crédits</title>
      <link>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/credits.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/credits.fr/</guid>
      <description>Contributeurs Merci à eux de rendre le monde Open Source meilleur !
Et un grand merci à @vjeantet pour son travail sur docdock, un fork de hugo-theme-learn. La v2.0.0 du thème est en grande partie inspirée de son travail.
Packages et librairies  mermaid - géneration de diagrames et graphiques à partir de texte similaire à Markdown font awesome - Le framework de polices iconiques jQuery - La plus connue des librairies Javascript lunr - Lunr fournit des fonctions de recherche sans service externe horsey - Autocomplétion de composants (utiliser pour les suggestions de recherche) clipboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/showcase/</guid>
      <description>TAT by OVH Tshark.dev by Ross Jacobs inteliver by Amir Lavasani </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vitrine</title>
      <link>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/vitrine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Erdan101.github.io/en/vitrine/</guid>
      <description>TAT par OVH Tshark.dev par Ross Jacobs inteliver by Amir Lavasani </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
